Joe Bentley

Profile

For the past 5 years I have been privileged to travel the world performing as a Showteam Leader and Dance Captain for TUI Cruises. I performed and danced in evening shows to in excess of 1,000 people regularly. Additionally, I led and managed teams through daily rehearsals and successful performances. Performing is my passion, but the job required other skills including organisational, administrative and technical skills.

From an early age I developed a keen interest in computing both hardware and software and this has continued to the present day, leading to a desire to progress and boost my knowledge in software application development. The recent pandemic led me to seek out relevant courses to further my career in this field.

Employment History

Showteam Dance Captain at Marella Cruises - 2019-2020

(Europe, Middle East, Indian Ocean, South East Asia)

Showteam Leader at Marella Cruises - 2017-2018

(Europe, Baltics, Caribbean)

Showteam Dancer at TUI Cruises - 2015-2016 (Europe including the Adriatic, Caribbean)

Shop Assistant at The Party Shop, Mold - 2011-2014

Education

Code Nation - Master Coding - 2020

KS Dance Ltd - 2011-2014

Alun School Sixth Form - 2009-2011

Alun School - 2004-2009

Ysgol-Y-Foel - 1999-2004

Qualifications

Level 6 Diploma in Professional Dance (DipTCL)

A Levels - Media Studies, and a full course (2 subjects) BTEC National Certificate in Performing Arts.

G.C.S.E's – English Language – C, English Literature – B, Maths – B, Biology – B, Chemistry – B, Physics – C, History – B, French – A, Physical Education – A, BTEC First Diploma in Performing Arts – 4x A*.

References

Paul Ainsworth – Producer, Peel Talent

paul.ainsworth@peelentertainment.com 07730768404

Susan Stewart - Hotel Operations Manager, Marella 07979934205

William Gough – Software Engineer – Utility Warehouse williamhenrygough@gmail.com. 07860529690

Details

Cilcain, Mold,

CH7 5PP

Date of Birth

20/08/1993

Nationality

British

Driving License

Full - Clean

Contact

01352740987

07545311812

joe.bentley.20@gmail.com

Skills

IT hardware, building PC's

IT software

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, REACT, Express, Python, Django, Git, Docker

Teamwork, Leadership